qome.com 2011-01-27

# 

**Privacy Policy**

**Overview**

By accepting the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal informationin the manner described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy took effect on April 1, 2002. This Privacy Policy was last updated on September 15, 2007.

**Data Protection**

Any information you provide us with will only be disclosed in accordance with the Data Protection Act of 1998. 

**TRUSTe Certification**

Quick Orbit E-Mony Ltd Ltd. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This covers the site www.Quick Orbit E-Mony Ltd.com. Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, Quick Orbit E-Mony Ltd has agreed to notify you of: 

  * What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information that is collected from you through the web site. 
  * The organization collecting the information. 
  * How the information is used. 
  * With whom the information may be shared. 
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information. 
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Quick Orbit E-Mony Ltd' control. 
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.   

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe through the TRUSTe WatchDog Dispute Resolution Process. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.

**Collection of Personal Information**

To open your Quick Orbit E-Mony Ltd account, we must obtain certain personal information, such as name, address, email or phone number as well as demographic information like age. For certain optional transactions, we also collect selected financial information such as credit/debit card details. For certain high amount transactions, we are legally required to report some personally identifiable information to the authorities. For verification purposes we reserve the right to request proof of identification in an offline format. Your IP address and access times are tracked against your user id for the dual purposes of preventing fraud and creating an audit trail when sending a payment, or logging onto our secure server. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site and do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. When sending money to a non-registered user, we will store the recipient's email address until either the recipient registers for a Quick Orbit E-Mony Ltd account or 14 days elapse. If the recipient does not register for an account, the email address will no longer be used by Quick Orbit E-Mony Ltd.

**Use of Personal Information**

We only use your personal information to service your account and to improve our services to you. However, we do share some financial information as part of normal business operations with banks or credit/debit card processing and verification services. These entities may not use your information for secondary purposes, unless required by law. Furthermore, when sending money to another Quick Orbit E-Mony Ltd account holder we will always pass on your email address to the recipient. Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. Otherwise, UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES will information you provide to Quick Orbit E-Mony Ltd be transmitted in any way to a third party.

**Control of Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct and update that user's personally identifiable information provided to us. This can usually be done by logging into your account and clicking on the "profile" link or by contacting our Customer Service Department. Your zip code, phone and postal address can only be changed once in any 3 month period. In order to deactivate your account your will need to contact our Customer Service Department. However, please understand we cannot completely delete user information because of legal/regulatory and technical back up requirements.

**Communication**

Upon registration every user will receive an email confirming his successful registration. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services and special deals via newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. This can usually be done by logging into your account and clicking on the "profile" link.

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Quick Orbit E-Mony Ltd is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Security**

Quick Orbit E-Mony Ltd secures your account information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. You must enter your email and password each time you want to access your account information or make transactions. Never share your account details with anyone. If you are concerned that your password has been compromised, you can change it any time you like once you are logged on. Your account login, personal details and all money transactions are secured using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology with high security 128bit encryption, certified by Verisign Secured. 

**Notification of Changes**

Changes to this privacy statement are posted here so you know what use is made of your information. If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice whether to use your information in this new manner. However, if you have opted out of all communication with the site, or deactivated your account, then you will not be contacted, nor will your information be used in this new manner.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:  
Email: [**privacy@qome.com**](mailto:privacy@qome.com)  
Telephone: +44 870 2881286  
Postal Address: Quick Orbit E-Mony Ltd,77, East Rd, London, N1 6AH 

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

**What the UK law requires:**

•We may be required to verify your identity and address.

•We are required to keep full records of all transactions together with identification provided.

•We are required to monitor any unusual or suspicious transactions of any size.

•We have a legal obligation to report to the Serious Organised Crime Agency (SOCA) any suspicious transaction.
